ABOUT ME

Graduate from the University of California, Irvine with a Bachelor of Science in Informatics with a specialization in Human-Computer Interaction. 2+ years of management experience. 5+ years of professional tech support experience. Diversified set of skills including management, UX research, UI design, web design, web dev, and graphic design.

EDUCATION

University of California, Irvine

SEPT 2013 – JUNE 2019 Bachelor of Science in Informatics Specialization: HCI

El Segundo High School

SEPT 2009 – JUNE 2013

SKILLS

Languages

Java Python



Design

Photoshop
Illustrator
InDesign



Prototyping

InVision
Balsamiq
Adobe XD
Sketch

Development

Dreamweaver
CSS3
HTML5
Javascript
React Native
jQuery

LINKS

LinkedIn: Icramer Github: laurencramer Website: laurenrenee.me

LAUREN CRAMER

☐ (310) 413-4509
☐ Icramer@uci.edu
⑦ Los Angeles

EXPERIENCE

Field Support Technician // Robert Half

FEB 2020 - MAR 2019 / LOS ANGELES, CA

Set up recently developed voting devices for the Los Angeles County primary election.

Followed strict technical and legal protocol mandated by the manufacturer and county.

Provided on-call technical support for voting devices and iPads during the election. Broke down and properly stored all devices post-election.

Operations Manager // Eskape Rooms OC

FEB 2019 - AUGUST 2019 / IRVINE, CA

Set up business and revenue software, including Quickbooks, customer appointment software, and employee scheduling software.

Hired entire staff and created employee work schedules.

Tracked company finances, revenue, expenses, and employee wages.

Resolved technical issues with office electronics and escape room tech.

IT Manager // Savage Enterprises

SEPT 2018 - FEB 2018 / IRVINE, CA

Assessed and integrated new software and services, such as Slack, time-tracking software, and Netsuite, depending on the needs of the company or needs of specific departments.

Troubleshooted networking equipment, Excel scripts, user systems, and business devices, such as Polycom phones and Zebra printers.

Evaluated processes and procedures of tech support staff.

Assessed workflows of other departments to help maximize efficiency of current software use.

Recommended new software and systems to multiple departments based on workflow observations.

Prepared and evalutated workflow solutions.

Created manuals for all departments for new and current software and procedures. Created user tests to determine which software or procedures would be most valuable for a given department.

Systems Analyst // Savage Enterprises

JUNE 2018 - SEPT 2018 / IRVINE, CA

Troubleshooted user systems, business devices, and business software.

Maintained and updated company tools, such as sales spreadsheets, Excel order form and sales commission scripts, CRMs, ERPs, and ecommerce software, like Shopify. Created manuals for multiple departments for current software, new software, and procedures.

Manager // Eskape Rooms Irvine

FEB 2017 - FEB 2018 / IRVINE, CA

Interviewed and hired employees and created employee schedules.

Tracked company finances, revenue, and employee wages.

Resolved technical issues with office electronics and escape room tech.

Computer Support Technician // HelloTech

AUG 2014 - PRESENT / SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA

Traveled to customers' homes to provide technical support for personal devices. Resolved various technical issues, such network connectivity and disfunctional devices.

Setup new devices, including smartphones, laptops, desktops, printers, routers, modems, and Apple TVs.

Explained to customers how the issue was resolved, how to troubleshoot it if the issue happens again, and how to prevent the issue in the future.